

ABOUT ME

I'm an organized and responsible person, always open to improvement.

In my last years of high school I gained work experience by participating in different ventures and I was distinguished as "Hope of the Homeland 2022".

Autonomously I improved and expanded my computer skills and I'm interested in further training in accounting, financial and administrative issues, and in ERP's and other similar software tools.



46.418.935





Unmarried







marcos_lorenzana@hotmail.com



+54 9 11 3762-3202



www.gabyxer.com



Lomas del Mirador, La Matanza, Province of Buenos Aires, Argentina.

COMPUTER SKILLS / TOOLS

Word Intermediate L. React Basic L.

Excel Intermediate L. ChatGPT Intermediate L.

PowerPoint Intermediate L. Firebase Basic L. Visual Studio Code Intermediate L.

HTML Intermediate L.

Wondersnare Filmora 12

Basic L.

CSS Intermediate L.

Canva > Basic L.

Da Vinci Resolve > Basic L.

Photoshop > Basic L.

JavaScript > Basic L.

MARCOS GABRIEL LORENZANA

PUBLIC ACCOUNTANT STUDENT

ACADEMIC TRAINING

National University of La Matanza

Degree Course: Public Accountant, 2023 - in progress

San José Obrero Institute

Bachelor in Economics and Administration, 2017 - 2022

- Academic average 9.37
- Distinction "Hope of the Homeland 2022"

WORK EXPERIENCE

Head of Administration and Finance Emparedadon't, July 2022 - November 2022

- Preparation of formal and commercial documentation of the company.
- Compilation and registration of legal and management information.
- · Elaboration and control of the budget.
- · Cost calculation.
- · Administration of economic resources.
- Planning and monitoring of collections and control of discounts.

Temporary Manager

Futuros Inflables, November 3, 2022

- · Preparation of tickets.
- · Supervision of the inflatable.
- · Customer care.

Accounting Management Manager

Sanjo Sabores, October 2021 - November 2021

- Preparation of formal and commercial documentation of the company.
- Registration of operations.
- Funds management.

LANGUAGES

